maxair.com.ng 2019-05-29

# Privacy policy | Max Air official website

This website is brought to you by Max Air Limited (Max Air).  Max Air respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. 

## Information Collection 

* * *

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, title, gender, birth date, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

When you browse our website, you do so anonymously, unless you have previously indicated that you wish Max Air to remember your login details. We do not automatically collect personal information, including your email address(s). We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our website.

Max Air collects personal information when you make a reservation, participate in an online survey, when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, or when you submit your personal information to Max Air for any other reason. From time to time, Max Air receives personal information from business partners and vendors. Max Air only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Policy and applicable laws. 

## How we may use your personal data 

* * *

When personal information is collected, we will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection (e.g. reservation, Marketing purposes, special promotions, etc.). Generally, the purposes include: 

  * To help us identify you
  * Administration
  * Improving our services
  * Statistical analysis
  * Billing and other fulfillment
  * Security vetting
  * Customer profiling and analyzing your purchase preferences
  * Fraud detection and prevention
  * To notify you of any changes to this website or our services which may affect you

Max Air will not transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the discussion entitled “Information Sharing and Disclosure” below. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure 

* * *

Your personal information is never shared outside Max Air without your permission, except under conditions explained below. Inside Max Air, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access. 

Max Air may send your personal information to other companies or people under any of the following circumstances: when we have your consent to share the information; we need to share your information to provide the service or booking you have requested; we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Max Air to provide the requested service to you (we will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose). We will also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, to enforce our Terms and Conditions, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our websites. 

## Data Security 

In certain areas of our websites, Max Air uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions (Powered by HITIT). While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy 

* * *

This Policy is subject to amendment from time to time as may be necessary for Max Air. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site. We advise you check this policy occasionally to ensure you are aware of the most recent version which will be applicable each time you access this website. 

## Questions or Suggestions 

* * *

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at info@maxair.com.ng or write to us at Max Air Limited, 16 Ashton Road, Kano, Kano State, Nigeria.
